And that's why today at my direction I'm
announcing Project Meridian.
An effort And that's why today at my
direction I'm announcing Project
Meridian.
>> Meridian.
>> An effort led by America's best minds to
study the future of warfare.
Under the leadership of the department's
chief technology officer, Emil Michael,
Project Meridian will be co-led by three
of our nation's best minds.
Elon Musk, Palmer Lucky, and N.
Gingrich.
>> Oh my god. Of
>> whom are up in the audience with us
today. [music] Please stand if you
would.
>> Oh my god.
>> Thank you.
>> Project Meridian.
>> And that's why today
>> Holy Okay. Um,
>> correction, the fourth announcement
[music] is the next great American base.
We haven't built a new base in this
country in 40 years. That ends now.
President Trump is a builder. And this
building,
beautiful, and world class for the great
Americans who wear our nation's uniform.
>> Uh-huh.
>> We're calling on every governor in the
country and agitant general, every tag
across this great republic to step up to
the plate and bring us their best sales
pitch. If your state wants the honor of
hosting 15 to 25,000 of America's great
troops, show us why and how you're going
to do it.
>> Cutting through the red tape, offering
up the land, and rolling out the red
carpet for our military families.
>> Oh boy.
>> Now, this is not going to be a soulless
government installation.
We will plan out and chart out a
dynamic, self-sustaining power
projection platform. We're talking
hundreds of thousands of acres with
organic power generation, modern air
defenses, and cutting edge technology.
Think a fortress.
>> Just as importantly, [laughter]
we are restoring pride and standards to
how our troops live.
>> Oh man. In line with the president's
executive order
>> on beautiful civic architecture,
>> this base will be a proud fortress of
our republic built with timeless
>> classical architecture.
>> Beautiful.
>> Our soldiers, our sailors, our airmen,
marines, and guardians will have clean
first class barracks, worldclass
training facilities, and thriving
communities with top tier housing,
school, child care, and healthcare for
families.
>> Yes,
>> we owe our warriors.
>> Is this part of the big plan?
>> Nothing less than the gold standard.
[music] It is
>> now this entire selection process.
>> This is absolutely part of the big plan.
>> Each of us committed to the nation with
the sentiment of the sixth chapter of
the book of Isaiah.
>> Oh boy.
>> Each of us committed to the nation with
the sentiment of the sixth chapter of
the book of Isaiah. Lord, here I am.
>> Send me. Send me to fight the red coats.
Send me to fight the communists. Send me
to fight the Islamists. Send me.
You see the Ivy League facity faculty
lounges.
[gasps]
Oh boy.
Oh
boy.
Holy.
>> You see the Ivy League facity faculty
lounges, they'll never understand you.
>> And that's okay cuz they could never
[music] ever do what you do.
>> Wow.
>> The media will mischaracterize you. And
that's okay.
>> Uhhuh.
>> Because deep down they know you're the
reason they live free. They envy [music]
you
>> because you do real things every single
day. Jesus,
>> you are the real 1%.
In the middle of the profession of arms,
each of us committed to
>> Jesus Christ. And okay, let me see here.
Project Meridian, Fortress America.
[laughter] Holy
[groaning]
[laughter]
But it's worth saying again so that the
fake news understands it. But it's worth
saying again so that the fake news
understands it. We are no longer the
woke department or the weak department.
Simple translation of that. No fatty no
fatties. No No beardos. No
weirdos. No wimps. No radicals.
>> [crying]
[laughter]
>> Simple translation translation of that.
No fanny, no fatties, no No
beardos, no weirdos, no wimps, no
radicals.
Weirdos, no wimps. No no
beardos. No weirdos, no wimps, no
radicals.
>> [panting and gasps]
[laughter]
>> Oh my god.
Wow.
Just warriors. Just tough, ready,
committed troops. The War Department, as
you know, is colorblind,
genderneutral, and merit-based.
Or as the president likes to say to me,
hate central casting.
I want central casting.
>> The ideological clowns are out. The
patriotic cowboys are in with
testosterone testing on top.
Holy
Oh [laughter] my god.
This is insane,
sir. The plan is in motion.
Oh my god.
Diversity is not our strength. Unity is
our strength. Because what that's all
that really matters when the missiles
are flying.
You see, the delusional media will
downplay all of the progress of the past
year, but this group right here, and I
look forward to hearing from you all
tomorrow morning as well, knows how real
and how important cultural change is and
has been.
No radicos, no weirdo. No fatties, no
No beardos, no weirdos. Fanny,
no fatties, no No beardos, no
weirdos. No fatties, no No
beardos. No weirdos. No wimps, no
radicals,
just warriors.
Holy
Oh my god.
I
that this this is insane.
Like I I
Holy
We need more officers from academic
institutions like our militarymies and
senior military colleges. And today
we're going to make that happen. Enter a
new core of cadetses.
To meet this critical need, we're
partnering with a new crop of premier
higher ed institutions,
including Louisiana State University,
LSU,
>> Liberty University,
Tuskegee University,
Mississippi State University,
>> Mhm.
>> and Hillsdale College.
These schools have stepped forward to
answer the call to duty.
>> You couldn't say any of this 20
years ago. Yeah, you could not say any.
This is See, everybody hates on Trump,
but like you got to keep in mind like
nobody could have gone up. This guy is
the Secretary of War and he's just going
out there and saying no fatties. We're
running it on testosterone. Diversity
isn't our strength
>> and establish new cores of cadetses in
partnership with the Department of War.
>> That's nuts.
>> So today, at my direction, we are
formally establishing a program live
secretary.
>> These universities and colleges.
>> That's right.
>> It's called America's core of cadets.
>> Wow.
>> This flagship effort is central to our
goal of increasing the number of
patriotic leaders of character who are
commissioned into our joint force.
>> Oh my god.
>> Each member school is designated a
distinguished military college, reviving
a category previously used in our
department.
>> You remember this guy? Yeah. This guy
also, by the way, has a Crusades uh
tattoo. And let me see if there's any
more of these. So, there's a new
project. Oh, God. Is this the armor? The
the armor of God,
and that [music] ends now. Today, at my
direction, I'm establishing the Office
of Religious Affairs.
Oh my god.
starting today and for secretaries of
war after me the office of religious
affairs
and that ends now today at my direction
I'm [music] establishing the office of
religious affairs
I think we might get the templars
like you know this now right that like
there's a universe in which he
reestablishes the templars
Like it it
>> starting today and for secretaries of
war after me the office of religious
>> I mean he's talking about like I mean
this is crazy like building a fortress
like the office of relig oh oh my god
>> affairs will report straight to the top
no staff filters no bureaucratic
dilution a direct line to the secretary
this is not going to be a paper pushing
shop it's going to have real
They'll protect budgets, demand
infrastructure, and strengthen religious
support. The experts,
>> man,
>> our chaplain will finally have an
advocate at the
I just guys
we're actually
before the experts, our chaplain will
finally have an advocate at the highest
levels. Policy and resources will serve
the mission, not smother the [music]
mission.
>> Oh my God.
>> As s Psalm 33:12 extols [music] us.
Blessed is the nation whose God is the
Lord.
250 years ago, we rejected an earthly
king an ocean away in appealing instead
to a heavenly king above.
George Washington made sure that the
Continental Army had chaplain back at
the beginning back in 1775.
>> Oh my.
>> That force appealed to heaven and we
still do today. Our national motto is
after all in God we trust.
Today we reaffirm that trust.
>> Man, this is not necessary. It is
it's complete cultural and it's a
complete cultural and uh
just a total cultural victory. It's it's
about establishing complete and absolute
total cultural control with there being
no
even inclination that there's anything
other than that.
That's why it that's why it's there.
>> We're placing spiritual health at the
same level as physical health.
>> Our department is, you might say,
putting on the full armor of God.
putting on
>> because while we wage physical war,
>> we all know the real battle is
spiritual.
>> God is good,
>> evil is not. And America's military must
understand the [music] difference.
Oh my god.
Um,
wow.
I
holy
I I really like I
That's insane. Like that was heavy. Like
I I didn't even expect I I like I I
didn't even know about this.
Like this is insane.
So we're bringing back paladins. We're
bringing back the Templars.
Like he's talking about bringing back
chaplain, having an entire like an
American military fortress.
Like I feel like this dude is five years
away from declaring a crusade.
Really?
You're talking about extremism rising in
the US and the next Adolf Hitler coming
up. Meanwhile, in the US, this isn't
extremism. This is normaly in America.
This is the way that it's supposed to be
here.
Like you just been you've been sigh up
by a bunch of hags that hate the country
and hate their dad that made you think
that this isn't what's normal.
No. Welcome back to the welcome back to
the old normal. Now back to the new
normal.
That's really the difference. Lord the
imperium of man. I know this is normal.
It's even in your constitution. Exactly.
Yeah. There's nothing extreme about
this. Yeah. You see this is the problem,
right? is like y'all have been spending
so much time in the cave thinking that
this stuff isn't extreme. This cool
video hexf in the morning leading
training in a Pentagon. Yeah. And by the
way, here's the most important thing.
Is it all the chuds?
All the chuds.
At least every chud that I know.
This is probably what the This might not
be what the military generals want to
hear. This might not be what the uh
Congress wants to hear, but the chuds
that are serving in the military that
have the boot that are the boots on the
ground that are sitting there in the
bases and they hear him saying no
fatties, uh no weirdos like
testosterone. I I'm sorry, guys,
but that's what they're waiting to hear.
They're thinking to themselves, "Oh,
thank God.
Oh, thank God. 100% facts. Yeah. I mean,
let's be real, right? And uh the Chud
Department, it is. And if if they let I
wonder what's going to happen if they
let him keep going. I do because
eventually the Iran war will be over and
then what what what is he going to do
after that? I'm really curious.
I mean, they've got over two more